Theme Tune: [music playing]
Al: Hello Farmers and welcome to another episode of The Harvest Season. My name is Al.
Codey: And my name is Codey.
Al: Excuse me, that's not what the script says.
Codey: My name is, uh, Durr-Codey.
Codey: Doctor... [laughs]
Codey: Doctor Codey, it me.
Al: This is your first episode since becoming officially, well, no, I guess, well, I don't
Codey: I'm the bug doctor! Woo!
Codey: I did the...
Codey: Oh my gosh.
Al: know, I don't know what, I feel like at some point in the past you were saying that you
Al: were a doctor and then, but you weren't finished. So I'm confused about what, how the process
Al: actually works, but the first one, since it's all finished.
Codey: So, yeah, yeah, yeah. So, basically, like, once you defend your dissertation, it's kind of just formality after that.
Codey: And so, I had defended and my committee was like, "Yes, you passed. Congratulations."
Codey: And they called me doctor at that point, but then this is now, like, I walked across the stage.
Codey: I turned in my dissertation. I actually just got the information today that my dissertation is now available on open access.
Codey: So, if anyone wants to read my dissertation titled Assessing the Impact of Floral Resources and Vertical Stratification on Insect Behavior and Biases of Common Trapping Methodologies for Insect Communities, you can find that.
Al: I'll be totally honest with you, Codey. I don't want to read it.
Codey: You know what? I don't blame you. I'm also not going to read it, so.
Al: You know, it's funny because Rona, my wife, she's a musician for people who don't know.
Al: And she did music teaching was her degree. And there were a bunch of people on her degree who
Al: wrote dissertations that she was very interested in. She was like, "Oh, get me a copy. I'd love
Al: to read that. She's not read a single book.
Al: She's read every single one since then, and it's been 13 years.
Codey: - Yeah.
Codey: Yeah.
Codey: Well, it's one of those things like it's super,
Codey: it is interesting and you're like,
Codey: oh my gosh, I'm gonna read this.
Codey: And then you try and sit down to read it.
Codey: And like some people,
Codey: I'm not entirely sure how long their dissertations were,
Codey: but I would say the average is somewhere
Codey: between like 100 pages to like more than 100 pages.
Codey: I don't know, like maybe 200 pages.
Codey: Mine is 500 pages long.
Codey: So I am not expecting anyone to read it,
Codey: But if you wanted to, it is a novel.
Al: like a novel. Rhona was such a nerd that she did two different dissertations. She did an
Codey: It feels like that, but if you wanted to read it, it's there, so find it.
Al: elective dissertation as well as her normal dissertation for some reason. Yes, she is
Codey: That...is...a choice.
Al: such a nerd. No, no, no. I don't know. Maybe it's not. Maybe this is one of those cultural
Codey: Wait, so she has a doctorate?
Al: things. We call dissertations for.
Al: Degrees. I don't know whether that's a cultural thing. I don't know whether you don't call
Codey: Okay.
Al: them dissertations when there's a degree, but we do here.
Codey: Is it- wait, so what level of degree did she get?
Al: Bachelors. Yes, she did. I can't remember whether this was one of our dissertations
Codey: Okay, cool. Still interesting.
Al: or just a different thing. She did something on video game music.
Codey: Ooh!
Al: So, yeah, anyway, music and Dr. Codey.
Codey: Music!
Codey: And it me! Woo!
Al: Not music. Bugs.
Codey: [laughs] Bugs!
Al: And we're here today to talk about Codeyscore games. Woo!
Codey: [sniffs] Ugh!
Codey: Oh, woo! Ow, ow, ow!
Al: This episode we're going to talk about news, because there's lots of news, including a
Al: lot of new games. Last episode I said there were only three more new games that we needed
Al: to talk about. And if there wasn't anything else new, then we wouldn't have a problem.
Al: And then Gamescom happened and 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, we have nine!
Codey: Yep.
Al: New games to talk about.
Codey: Thanks, Gamescom.
Al: So, and it's very possible I've missed something, because I was not looking through all the
Al: Gamescom stuff manually. I was, like, searching for stuff.
Codey: I will say some of these, I would personally not qualify as cottagecore.
Al: Look, look, well, I'll be honest with you, I haven't looked into them.
Codey: Okay, cool, we will decide on the fly.
Al: Why not? That's what this episode is. This episode is cottagecore or not.
Codey: Woo-hoo!
Al: So we're going to talk about all the new games. There's also some game news as well. I think
Codey: [laughing]
Codey: Heck yeah!
Al: there's more new games than there is game news, but there's still game news. Some reasonably
Al: big game news as well. And then we also have I Know What You Released Last Month because
Al: it is September as you're listening to this. So we've got all of August. Let's forget about
Al: the fact that we're actually recording this on the last day of August and so therefore
Al: technically it's this month. But before all of that, Codey, what have you
Codey: Nah, it's fine.
Al: been up to?
Codey: I graduated and moved!
Codey: So I now live in an area of New Jersey in which we can quickly get to Manhattan.
Codey: So Al, if you and Rona ever want to come to the Big Apple, New York City, you got a place to stay.
Codey: I got a nice couch.
Al: I think it's very likely that at one point I will,
Al: I think it's probably less likely Runa will, but who knows? We will see.
Codey: That's fine.
Codey: Well, at least for the next year.
Codey: Unless I get...
Codey: Okay.
Al: It won't be in the next year. I can guarantee you that it will not be in the next year.
Codey: Cool.
Codey: Well, yeah, so we moved, and my new apartment is questionable.
Codey: I've had many not great interactions with my landlady.
Codey: The most recent of which, I told her that I saw a cockroach.
Codey: The most recent of which, I told her that I saw a cockroach and she was like...
Codey: "I've never had cockroaches at my properties. I don't think you saw a cockroach."
Codey: And I was like, "Ma'am, I'm an entomologist. Please, I think I know what the heck I'm talking about."
Codey: And I actually collected it, because of course I did, and I looked at it under a microscope
Codey: and took photos of it under a microscope and sent it to her and looked it up and was like,
Codey: "Oh, it's this tawny cockroach or spotted Mediterranean cockroach."
Codey: It's like Ectobius pallidus, I think is the scientific name.
Codey: Um, and I was like, so I don't think it's, it's, it's like a non invasive,
Codey: non pest one it's introduced to the area, but it's not like going to be
Codey: something that's going to be a pest in the house.
Codey: So I don't think it's an issue.
Codey: And she was like, okay, I'll send this to my exterminator.
Codey: And then she comes back to me and this was after she she's like, she's like, I'll
Codey: send this, the photo of the bug to my exterminator.
Codey: And I'm like, I just didn't say anything.
Codey: And then she's like, so how often have you been coming back
Codey: and forth from Pennsylvania?
Codey: And I'm like, I mean, not too often, but also like this species is, is local to
Codey: Long Island and has been making its way West of, from Long Island, like onto
Codey: Manhattan and now into Jersey.
Codey: So like, this isn't a Pennsylvania species.
Codey: And then she was like, well, my exterminator says it's a Pennsylvania
Codey: wood roach and she, she didn't outright say, but she basically
Codey: insinuated that we brought it.
Codey: Um, which, you know, if that makes her feel better in her heart.
Codey: Uh, sure.
Codey: Um, so there's that.
Codey: Have been playing.
Codey: So I, we had a, a debacle of, I started playing this game called big, bad Pharma.
Codey: Um, which is a super cute game on the, on Steam.
Codey: It's just, it's one of the sorting games.
Codey: So I don't know what we're calling these yet.
Codey: If there, if we're calling them library likes, because there's the library game
Al: I feel like we can have a better name than that, surely. Or Organizers. Cozy Organizers.
Codey: that everyone knows about, which is librarian tardy, tidy up the arcane library.
Codey: than library-like. Organizers sorting...
Codey: Yeah, we could have a whole episode about cozy organizers and I could cover...
Al: Nobody. Actually no, it can't be Cozy Organizers because then when people define their genre
Codey: I have played... So I've played the library game.
Al: as Cozy Organizers I'll get annoyed because they're calling it cozy. And no, it can't
Codey: You don't think it's cozy?
Al: be that. So I just, well no I guess my point is like I always, I get annoyed when people
Al: say that their game is cozy, right? Oh here's a cozy game. And I'm like no that's for the
Codey: Mm, correct.
Al: players to decide. And so if we say that the genre is Cozy Organizers and then they say
Al: oh this is a Cozy Organizer, they are saying that it's cozy. That's the problem. Organizers.
Codey: Mm-hmm, got it.
Codey: So just organizing, sorting games, I think is what Steam calls it.
Al: Sorting games. Yeah I mean I think the thing is that sorting games I often think of like
Codey: So...
Al: which is on a much smaller scale, right? There's like different kinds, there's organizing on
Codey: No, it's lovely.
Al: the unpacking scale and then there's this which is like Hellscape.
Codey: So the library game is 4,000 books are scattered on the floor all over the place.
Codey: You have to put them back in their correct section and correct shelf.
Codey: And then I've also played Supermarket Chaos, which is same, same, but it's a supermarket.
Codey: And they have three different maps.
Codey: So there's a map with like 3,000, a map with like 1,000, and then a map with 10,000.
Al: Oh, I think I know what you're about to talk about because I'm looking at the news section.
Codey: at Big Bad Pharma.
Codey: Oh, I didn't.
Codey: Is there something about it?
Codey: Oh, this would be great.
Codey: So I I haven't looked at what you're talking about.
Al: Well, tell me what you're telling me. Tell me what your issue
Codey: So my thing is that we were I played it a good amount.
Codey: And then I left it here for the last week in Pennsylvania,
Codey: because like here in Jersey, because I didn't need it.
Codey: And then I went back to play it yesterday.
Codey: And Jeff's Steam account is locked.
Codey: This Steam account is locked.
Codey: because it says that his American Express disputed the claim of $6.67 for this game.
Codey: And so we reached out to his Amex and his Amex was like, "No, we don't have an issue with this.
Codey: I don't know what they're on about." And so then we went back to Steam and we were like,
Codey: "Amex doesn't have a problem with this charge. Please just give me my game back."
Codey: and it says like specifically you know if this was if this is made an error
Codey: just let us know and then you can rebuy the game but like his account is like
Codey: straight-up blocked like I can't we can't buy anything new until we fix that
Codey: issue is that what the news is about
Al: - No, no, no.
Al: So their second most recent news is entitled,
Al: "No AI Art Left in Big Bad Pharma."
Codey: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Al: [laughing]
Al: So it's not "No AI Art" in the game,
Al: it's "No AI Art Left" in the game.
Al: [laughing]
Codey: >> Yeah. Well, so I think that they had used it, they had used art to make the like pill
Al: Classic.
Codey: bottle labels. And but yeah, it's gone. And that's that's something that's really important.
Al: - Mm-hmm.
Codey: Like people have been really trying to consider these games, these sorting games, and if they're
Codey: using AI or not, because it people could very quickly use AI and like generate all of these
Codey: things. And...
Codey: And this is a big like people are spending a lot of time like I it says that I spent 98 hours in this game
Codey: I don't believe that
Codey: Because I only had it for like a week and a half
Codey: And so if I was spending 98 hours, I'd have to play it like 10 hours a day
Codey: And there is no way that I was doing that
Codey: So, yeah, I don't know but I really enjoy it that's a fun one so
Codey: Yeah, what about you? Oh, what have you been up to?
Al: I have been playing the Pocopia DLC. I will have thoughts on that at some point. Will
Al: they be what listeners are expecting them to be? Who knows? We shall find out. I think
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: Ooooooooh!
Al: that's all I've been playing just now. I'm trying to think. Yeah. I've been reorganizing
Al: a bunch of stuff so I redid my ethernet cables in my house today because I had, yeah, because
Codey: Ooh, that, so satisfying.
Al: they've done some...
Al: something's wrong with my setup and I was like, "Hmm, something's wrong because I'm only getting like about 100 meg, just under 100 meg on my Wi-Fi, which is not right. That's not... it should be much more than that. I do have an older Wi-Fi system, but it should be close to half a gig because I'm on a gigabit internet and the Wi-Fi that I have should be getting at least half a gig, which I've been looking into upgrading to a better Wi-Fi to be able to get the full gig, but that's a whole other question. So I'm like, "Something's wrong here." So I was like, "You know what? I have... every
Codey: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Al: single cable in my house is like a different type of cable, a different one. I've no... one of them must be... must be an old Cat5 cable, so let me replace everything." I can't replace everything because the cable out to my office is like under the ground, but that's a Cat5e, so it supports gigabit anyway. So that's fine for just now. I'll need to replace it at some point, but that is not a "for now" job when I only have gigabit internet. That's a future job. So I bought a bunch of
Codey: Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Al: eight cables and replaced them all, all my existing cables, and now today I was getting half a gig on Wi-Fi. So I want to do a little bit more in my office where my... like I have my desk and laptop connected to a USB hub, but which is connected to my monitor, but it's not connected to ethernet. It's just going off Wi-Fi,
Codey: Yay! Oh, I don't--
Al: because it's a standing desk and cables are a little bit weird when you do that, and my Wi-Fi router in this room is on the other side of the room, so I'll need to move it over and like mount it onto my desk, so I only have one cable coming off it. So that is my plan at some point, which I have been designing some 3D-printed plans for that, because I have... underneath my desk I have a mounting system, which is a 3D-printed mounting
Al: which is fun for mounting up. I have all my cables and stuff in channels and stuff.
Al: It's really nice and tidy. Neat and tidy. That's what I was looking
Al: forward to say. But if I'm gonna add my router to that it needs to be done
Al: properly so I've been designing that. But that will mean that I could get my I
Al: could get my laptop up to a gigabit instead of half a gigabit on my desk. So
Al: All my cables match now, they're all nice, they're...
Al: little one meter Cat 8 cables that were surprisingly cheap because I read everywhere that Cat 8 can be really expensive, but they were pretty cheap, and I shouldn't have to replace them for a long, long time because they support up to 10 gigabit, so I can't see any time soon needing more than 10 gigabit, so that is nice.
Codey: I don't know, nowadays with the just exponential expansion of technology, who knows?
Al: Yeah, I mean, you're right, who knows? However, network speeds have generally gone up pretty
Al: slowly compared to everything else, right? Like, I'm on gigabit and I've been on gigabit now for a
Al: few years and, you know, it's not really… I mean, yeah, there are some places that have, that can get
Al: 10 gigabit, but I can't. Like, I'm not in a city. I won't be able to get 10 gigabit for a long time.
Al: So, yeah, I don't think that will be a problem, but I'm looking forward to having some…
Al: That would be nice.
Codey: Oh, whoo. Yeah, I just checked because I haven't checked since we moved to the new place and I am a
Codey: Like half a gig download speed right now, which is great
Al: Nice. Nice, nice, nice. It's nice because this place, when I first moved into it, it didn't have
Al: fibre and the non-fibre would only go up to, I think it was 10 megabit. It was pretty pathetic.
Al: So we didn't even get like 70 meg or anything, it was 10 meg. And then there was one cable company
Al: in the UK and so they... I know, I know. There's basically two places you can get internet. There's
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: How lovely.
Al: the phone line company, which is BT, and then there's the cable company, which is Virgin,
Al: and everyone else uses BT, right? They all use the BT lines. Virgin are the only other company
Codey: Oh.
Al: that does lines. So eventually, like maybe three or four years after we moved here, Virgin put in
Al: the cable and then so we were like, oh fantastic, we can actually get something decent. And it took
Al: till last year before BT upgraded our possibility internet. So now we actually can choose.
Al: I'm going to have a field day looking for the best deal. That'll be great. But yeah,
Codey: Wow
Al: up till now it's just been, it had to be Virgin because there was no other option.
Codey: I just had the hellscape that is trying to leave Comcast.
Codey: I tried to do that today.
Codey: Well, I did it today, but it was...
Codey: They're like, they're notorious for...
Codey: We try and leave and they're like, "Are you sure?
Codey: We could save you a lot of money. Where are you moving?
Codey: Why are you moving? What are you doing?
Codey: What about... Who's moving into this place?
Codey: Maybe we could save it. You've been with us for so long.
Codey: We could save you money."
Codey: And I literally just at one point was like,
Codey: Sir, I know that this is your--
Codey: But you guys would literally have to give me money every month to make it worth it. You're not gonna do that
Codey: I am so sorry. Please don't waste your time anymore
Al: Do you want to be jealous? So there's a law here that means that
Al: if I sign up with a new internet provider
Al: they do all of the work of getting the other company to disconnect.
Codey: Oh, that's so good.
Al: So you just sign up and you say yes I'm confirming I want to switch my internet
Al: over and then it just it just all happens.
Codey: You basically sick the other internet company on the... They can do it.
Al: Yeah and of course they will do whatever they need to do to do it because they
Al: one year, right? So it's great.
Codey: Yeah. Oh, that's so funny. Oh my gosh, I wish.
Al: Yeah, I know. I know it's dreadful. I hate because the Virgin do the thing that a lot
Codey: Because, yeah, that was a half an hour of my life that I'll never get back.
Al: of companies do, which is where they give you a like a two year contract, but it's like
Al: at half price. So after two years, the price doubles, you phone them up and you say, I'm
Codey: Yeah, yes, yes.
Al: leaving and they say, Oh, well, we can give you this price and it's the same price you
Al: were paying before, and so you go back down to it.
Codey: Yep.
Al: It just means that every two years you have to phone them up to change back to what you
Al: were paying before, and it's entirely because people will forget and just continue to pay
Codey: Well, and, but...
Al: more money, but it's just so scammy and so dreadful.
Codey: Yep.
Codey: Well, and then also, like, if you...
Codey: You might be, like, grandfathered into some service or something.
Codey: Like, you get...
Codey: Even though the amount is gonna go up,
Codey: you're gonna get free something or other.
Codey: but if you re-up with them and they give you the...
Codey: a deal again, it resets you back to the new thing and then you don't have that deal anymore
Al: And then of course you're on a new two-year contract so you can't switch
Codey: and it's just like, "Oh, you guys are the worst."
Al: until after another two years.
Codey: Yeah, I'm happy that we're not really on contracts anymore here.
Al: Nice.
Codey: You might be able to do that, but we are not.
Codey: So, woo!
Al: Yeah it's pretty it's pretty standard here that you kind of to get the good
Al: deals you have to be. And that's why I'm not switching internet provider till
Al: next year. Whoo. All right. That's what we've been up to. Let's talk.
Codey: Oh, woo!
Codey: [laughing]
Al: I know what you released last month. I'm really bad at introducing this
Al: section because it doesn't doesn't really fit grammatically. Because I
Al: can't I can't talk to you about it right because it's not what you released. Right?
Codey: what you released last month.
Al: Because the previous one is I ask you what you've been up to. It's like who am
Al: I asking? Who am I telling? I know what you released last month. It was a great
Al: idea when I came up with it but it doesn't really fit. It doesn't really work.
Codey: I know what was released last month, but then that, yeah, that doesn't really fit either.
Al: Yeah, but then you lose the-
Codey: You're right.
Codey: Listeners, hit us up if you have a new suggestion for the title of the monthly release segment.
Al: hey game devs I know what you released last month that's gonna that's gonna be so exhausting to say
Codey: Ayyy!
Codey: [laughs]
Al: in you know every month anyway uh first up we have three 1.0 releases um that is fields of
Al: mystria released their 1.0 exactly two years after their early access launched which is very satisfying
Al: dalek town released their 1.0 and star sand island giving me some points in the draft
Al: also released their 1.0 now here's a problem this is where we lead to a problem that i'm
Codey: Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Al: gonna have to think about is what does star sand island count for in the game
Al: of the year episodes do they count for early access 1.0 or both
Codey: Because they both came out this year.
Codey: Yeah, I would just do both.
Al: okay okay
Codey: Because like it's it did the early access came out this year
Codey: But it also came out like the 1.0 also came out this year. So I I would say both
Al: correct yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay it's not gonna win either
Codey: It's not gonna win
Al: but
Codey: I'm like, it's not it's not an issue
Al: it's not the point it might you never know it was fun
Codey: It's not
Al: um we also got lose lagoon and spirit stead they both released their uh first versions were which
Al: were not early access but they've released so they're they're out now and we have one early
Al: Early Access, which is Maisie Village, have released their first.
Al: version of their Early Access.
Codey: I feel like Lose Lagoon was one that I wanted to look up, and now I'm possibly more available with life, so...
Al: Yes.
Al: I mean absolutely feel free to try it. I will say it's Steam reviews are mixed.
Codey: Their website is called LuGuide, and that's adorable.
Al: I want it to be good
Codey: Mm-hmm.
Al: There's no more to that statement
Codey: Period.
Al: Um, yeah
Codey: Okay.
Al: Let's talk about some news
Al: for
Al: First up pokopia have released a new cloud island for the pokemon xp
Al: Which is their event that's going on at the same time as world championships, which is over by now
Al: But presumably the island will still exist
Al: so
Codey: Is this what you said you've been playing?
Al: Uh, I mean, I haven't, I haven't, this is not the deal.
Codey: No, this is not the DLC.
Al: This is just a new cloud island to visit.
Al: The DLC came out weeks ago.
Codey: Cloud- Cloud Islands being, like, islands, like, on an Animal Crossing that you can visit.
Al: Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Codey: Okay. I am so far behind on this game, and I am not worried about catching up.
Al: No, no, that's fine.
Al: So, so they released a bunch of like developer islands where you can go and see a bunch of
Al: stuff and they've kind of got some nice, so one of the developer islands had like a, a
Al: fun system where you could go in a minecart and go around and it would do some stuff with
Al: water and stuff.
Al: It's quite fun seeing what they had thought of in terms of being able to use the game.
Al: And then there was the Ikea one for some reason.
Codey: Oh my gosh.
Al: And I didn't have any Ikea items, but it was a thing for some reason.
Al: And then there's this one which is set up like the world championships.
Codey: Okay, cool.
Al: So there you go.
Al: Next up, Moonlight Peaks have released a small update.
Al: And I'm only really mentioning this because we mentioned the opposite of what happened
Al: in this in the last update.
Al: So me and Chelsea were talking about how...
Al: they had just released an update that nerfed a bunch of sell rates for things.
Al: Well, in this update they said...
Al: they also upgraded bulk cooking to be even more bulky.
Al: Yeah, I don't think I mentioned this in the last episode, they added
Al: bulk cooking because previously cooking was really annoying.
Al: It was just you could only do one at a time and it was really slow because it
Al: had a little minigame. The minigame... I don't remember
Al: whether we talked about the cooking minigame but it was
Al: fine. I didn't hate the cooking minigame but it was just really slow because you
Al: had to do it one at a time. Whereas now you can do up to 25 at once
Al: which is much, much better.
Codey: We do be lovin' some bulk.
Codey: So this is one that I like, 'cause I heard, so seeing them say, "We heard your feedback,"
Codey: I was like, "Oh, oh heck, that probably means that you got some real bad stuff."
Al: Yeah
Codey: And the top review, literally it says, "Most helpful reviews," is someone on the 21st of
Codey: August saying, "I loved Moonlight Peaks.
Codey: I genuinely looked forward to playing it every day, which is what makes me leaving a negative
Codey: review so disappointing.
Codey: And this person had played 121 hours at the review time and basically it was
Codey: about the nerf and how the nerf sucked which I'm I just like like I'm a little
Codey: like do we leave reviews or do we just should we just do discussion like
Codey: community thing at that point because now someone who's coming into this game
Codey: Like, because they just fixed it, right?
Codey: Like, in this new, new, uh...
Codey: update that they just posted.
Codey: But, if someone wanted to come and play this game
Codey: now, they would come and they just see
Codey: this incredibly negative review.
Codey: Top, front, and center.
Codey: Um...
Codey: I don't know, part of me is like, should we leave
Codey: this kind of feedback as a review
Codey: versus... especially because this is something
Codey: that's, like, temporary, you know?
Al: Yeah, it's a it's a difficult thing, right? Because I think reviews, like a bunch of negative reviews after an update, do certainly
Al: encourage developers to reverse course on unpopular decisions. The problem is
Al: that when you then go back and fix that,
Al: people don't update their reviews.
Al: Because the second top one is the exact same. It's saying I wouldn't recommend this game anymore after the new update.
Al: There's no point in nerfing prices in a single player cozy game.
Codey: Yeah.
Al: So like, yeah, the top two are both about the same thing and neither of them have been
Al: edited since that, which they dealt with your problem.
Al: So like, fix your review.
Al: You know, if you still don't recommend it because of other reasons, that's fine.
Al: But like, if you're going to, yeah, if you're going to make leave a review based on an update,
Al: then update your review based on another update, right?
Al: Like, that's only fair, surely.
Codey: Yeah, or have it say, like, "This is just at the time" or something like that.
Codey: And I guess, like, the first person says, "I'm shelving it, I really hope the developers reconsider these economy changes."
Codey: Yeah, I don't know. It's like, "You just left?" What? Anyway.
Codey: Well, glad that they fixed it, because it sounds like they had a good amount of people who were really enjoying the game,
Codey: and this really bummed him out so hopefully they can reel those people in.
Al: Yeah. Yes, all the comments on the patch update are very positive.
Al: Story of Seasons and Rune Factory. I've bundled these together because
Al: they're so small, but there was, last week, on my birthday, an anniversary - was it 30th
Al: anniversary? I think - of Story of Seasons live stream, and most of it was just like,
Al: "Aren't we great?"
Al: "Aren't our games great?"
Al: Blah, blah, blah, blah, sure, fine.
Al: Incredibly boring.
Al: Three hours long!
Codey: [laughs]
Al: I watched the entire thing!
Al: And then right at the end,
Al: right at the end of this three hours,
Al: they show a 10-second clip of stuff for the new games.
Al: Sadly, not enough to make me think
Al: that the game's actually coming out this year,
Al: R.I.P. my last game on my game draft,
Al: but yeah the...
Al: So a little clip, so if you want to look at it, Codey, it's in the show notes, if you instead of clicking on the embedded video, if you instead click on the video into YouTube, it should take you to the time, but it will be at 1 hour 20 minutes, gets the RuneFactory one.
Codey: Oh. Oh. Oh. It sure says starting.
Al: If you go to 1 hour 20 minutes, it will get you to that.
Codey: Oh my goodness, one hour.
Codey: I also am so awful at watching things in real time ever since I've been listening to podcasts
Codey: on two times.
Al: So you get a little like 10 second clip of Rune Factory stuff and it's uh you've got the little
Al: I can't remember what woolies I think they're called there's some woolies walking around you
Codey: Mm-hmm (affirmative).
Al: see a little farm plot you see a town it looks like quite a big built up town um and then some
Al: more woolies walking around and and that's it that's that's not even the name of a game it's
Al: just just uh assumption that it's rune factory because it's woolies and then
Codey: Yeah. Okay it just started. I love how it's not even game footage, it's like pretty footage.
Al: And then at 1 hour 21 and 55 seconds
Codey: Okay.
Codey: blue blue and 20 how many seconds yum yum yum yum yum okay
Al: uh 55
Al: we get a little hint of the next story of seasons game
Al: footage is representative of work in progress it says you see some seagulls flying over some water
Codey: Yeah.
Al: a town you see some farm plots uh you see some crops some lettuce some strawberries
Al: um but then and then it's it's evening the sun is setting it's night time there's lights
Codey: Some cherry trees, a dock.
Codey: Big ol'-- big cows.
Al: and then you got the cows and the chickens as usual the same cows and chickens as always
Al: and then that's it
Codey: For real? For real? Okay, that's...
Al: that's it and though we don't get a name for either of
Codey: Was it worth it?
Al: games we don't get nope it was not worth three hours um I don't know why this this is interesting
Codey: [laughs]
Al: because this is the this is the the u.s stream the japanese one was longer and this is just an
Al: hour and a half this american one I watched the entirety of the japanese one so that is all we
Al: know about the upcoming rune factory presumably rune factory 6 and the upcoming story of seasons
Codey: And that, that doesn't give you any points for your draft, so.
Al: Who knows when they'll come out?
Al: No, it does not, it does not.
Al: But I am still beating you right now.
Al: So next we have Farming Simulator 25.
Codey: No!
Al: They've announced their beans and alpacas expansion.
Al: And can you guess what it includes?
Codey: Uh, crocodiles and parrots!
Al: [laughs]
Codey: The joke is that it does also include crocodiles and parrots.
Codey: But yeah, this is basically an expansion that is South America inspired is what it says.
Codey: And you basically go to a new area that is based in South America and looks like South
Codey: America.
Codey: And you have a bean farm and alpaca walking around.
Codey: There's also Brahman cows.
Codey: Like, just cute cows.
Al: Obviously.
Codey: And then it says crocodiles and parrots, but I didn't see any in the trailer.
Codey: And I'm really concerned about, or not, because it said, they said something like,
Codey: "They make the world richer," or like, "Make the world seem more vibrant," or whatever.
Codey: And I'm like, okay, but like, do we have to worry about our alpacas and crocodiles?
Codey: Like, this is important information.
Al: Yeah.
Codey: So, and they have not addressed, I don't see an answer to that question, so.
Codey: Because if they're just for decoration, if they're just like, chilling, then it's fine.
Codey: But if it's like, "Don't put your alpaca farm near the water," like, that's pretty gruesome.
Al: Which does feel like a farming simulator thing, right?
Codey: Oh, you're right, you're right.
Codey: Yeah, this is Farming Simulator we're talking about, so.
Al: Yeah, so it said, "Wild animals like crocodiles and parrots bring more life to the environment."
Codey: But, yeah.
Codey: So, I guess not more death to the environment, so maybe we're fine.
Al: Well, who knows? Maybe both.
Codey: But, yeah, October of this year, just a month away.
Al: Yeah, and it's twenty six pounds
Codey: Wild.
Codey: I hate, I hate that.
Codey: That's a no from me, dog!
Al: However, if you don't already own farming simulator 25 you can buy a bundle that includes it for
Al: Was that 43 pounds
Al: But this is here's the so here's the mad thing
Codey: That's still a "no" from me.
Al: So the farming simulator 25 is currently listed on steam with no discount for 26 pounds
Codey: Mm-hmm.
Al: This expansion is 26 pounds
Al: Are we saying that this expansion includes as much content as the base game?
Codey: Well, it's basically just a whole new area.
Al: Yeah, but that's like the same price
Codey: I don't know. There's no logic.
Codey: There's no logic in this place.
Al: Next up petite planet as Codey writes here. This is the Hoyo verse
Al: farming game
Codey: [laughs]
Al: They have announced that it is coming in winter winter of 2026
Codey: Al, I specifically wrote "Oh damn, Hoylmer!"
Al: You
Al: Yeah, you're acting like you've not seen this before I also saw like how your verse announced like six games or something in a gamescom
Codey: Oh my god, my goodness.
Al: Slow down guys, come on
Codey: They're just really making sure that they don't want to slow down this money train.
Codey: I feel like, especially if they have a lot of people playing their other games,
Codey: it is probably an easy thing to pull people over.
Codey: I'm sure that they're going to do things like
Codey: play both of these games and get in-game blah blah blah blah blah.
Al: So there's a new trailer for this game as well. As of now we still don't know
Al: where the gacha is coming in
Codey: Mm-hmm, but we know it's coming.
Al: Presuming it's going to be gacha. They haven't actually officially said it, but let's let's be honest
Codey: Hoyovers.
Al: Yeah, so there's a lot still to know about this game, but winter 2026 now
Al: It's not winter 2026/2027. They're saying winter 2026. So that would imply December
Codey: To me, winter 2026 implies, like, when is the solstice?
Codey: Octo?
Codey: No.
Al: No, December.
Codey: November, I think.
Codey: November 21st?
Al: No, December. December 25th.
Codey: Or is it in December?
Codey: Oh my goodness.
Codey: Well in my brain, it's uh, when I think winter, I think November.
Al: So well, so here's the thing so do we got to have the
Al: The seasons discussion again, do we there are different definitions of seasons, right?
Al: And one of them does mean starting on
Al: Winter starting on this on the winter solstice. I think that one is stupid because like most most of winter has gone by that point
Codey: Yeah, I concur.
Al: It's basically Christmas, right? Like that's the middle of winter. That's not the not the beginning of winter madness to me
Al: Personally, my favorite.
Al: definition of the seasons is the 4-2-4-2, so summer and winter being four months,
Al: and autumn and spring being two months. But I know a lot of people don't like that.
Codey: I mean, I don't like it because I want the I want it to be reversed.
Codey: I want winter and summer to last two months, but you can't.
Al: Well, I actually, yeah, I mean, I agree with you, but that, that is, that is not a problem
Al: with definitions. That's a problem with the way the earth spins.
Codey: That frickin' earth, man, she's just ruining lives.
Al: I actually, I've talked a long time about how I don't hate summer and I don't hate winter.
Al: I just wish they were quicker. I don't, I just wish the year was half its current length.
Al: Like see if the year was six months, not a year, not 12 months. And then like winter
Al: like two months each. And then it's like, you're getting through these seasons quicker.
Al: It's cause my problem is not the heat or the cold. My problem is they just feel like they're
Al: lasting forever. And it's like by, by the beginning of August, I'm like, I'm done with
Codey: Yeah.
Al: the heat. Can we get rid of the heat, please give me some cold. And then by January I'm
Al: like, no, it's been dark and cold for months. Give me some sun. Right? So that's my problem.
Al: It's just everything lasts too long, I want the year to be faster.
Codey: Well, as a scientist who's part of the, uh, the big conglomerate of, like, blah blah,
Codey: 'cause we control the weather, right?
Codey: There's scientists and other people who control the weather.
Al: You want us to speed the earth up?
Codey: I'll get on it.
Codey: [laughs] Wee!
Al: How, well here's an interesting question. This is quite the tangent and I really should not be
Al: making tangents because it's 10pm, I want to go to bed. But if we could speed up the earth,
Al: but big assumption, if we could consistently speed up the earth to make it to double the speed
Al: so that it's going around the sun twice as fast. Let's forget about what that was.
Codey: Ugh. Okay. Okay.
Al: mean for orbit. Just forget about that for a minute. How quickly could we speed the Earth
Al: up without having disastrous environmental consequences?
Codey: None.
Codey: So even if, like, even if you speed it up, like, a week, say a week, there are some,
Codey: there's gonna be some species that are reliant on certain environmental conditions, and those
Codey: conditions are gonna last for a smaller amount of time, like a narrower window, and that
Codey: species is gonna get hecked up.
Codey: And that's stuff that's going to happen like over and over and over in all of the
Codey: ecosystems of the world and it's just going to mess us up so the answer is none.
Codey: We have all evolved to be a 365 quote day, sorry year, and have the seasons that we have
Codey: so evolutionarily we would be very upset.
Al: right okay but hear me out more christmases
Codey: Okay, I don't celebrate Christmas.
Al: more birthdays
Codey: I especially don't celebrate birthdays.
Codey: I'm not the right person to say holidays to.
Al: wouldn't it be great if we could all live to 200 i'm just lengthening all our lives here
Codey: Other people, no, no.
Codey: Dude whenever someone's like oh we're going to live forever like I'm going to increase
Codey: my lifespan I'm like man no or like become a mortal I'm like nah at a certain point I'm
Codey: going to be like I'm done.
Al: Do you know the worst one of those? Well yeah, I agree with you. I wouldn't want to be immortal.
Al: I would like to be theoretically immortal with the ability to decide to end my life at any point.
Codey: Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Al: So it's like you can live for as long as you want but then you can be like I'm done now.
Al: I would like that. No, the worst one is the guy, I can't remember his name, but there's a guy
Al: who's like does, he's like super famous for being like doing all these things that you know would
Al: would extend your life theoretically.
Codey: Mm-hmm.
Al: If you had a child basically as an organ donor?
Codey: [gasps]
Al: You're like, this is dreadful.
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: That is unethical!
Al: Yes, yes it is.
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: Isn't there...
Al: But then a lot of things that people do are unethical, so.
Codey: I feel like there's a whole movie about that,
Codey: about, like, some—not having it for—a kid for it,
Codey: but, like, having...
Codey: they have two children and one of their children
Codey: kind of just becomes, like, a blood donor
Al: Yeah, yeah, no, I don't know. Yeah, I remember that. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know whether that one's based on a true story or not
Codey: for the other one or something like that.
Al: But yeah, I don't remember what you're talking about. All right, that's petite planet
Codey: (laughs) Yeah.
Al: New trailer go check it out
Al: I've also seen a bunch of people talking about it because the beta is
Al: Like there's a private beta and so I've seen some people talking about how it works
Al: Obviously, it doesn't have the gacha stuff in it. There's a bunch of features that are just like coming
Codey: Does it have- so the- in the trailer, the little bit of a trailer,
Codey: you know what? I can- you don't have to do the emotional labor for me.
Codey: I can look that up later myself. Never mind.
Al: But is it an interesting discussion or not?
Codey: Well, so the beginning of the trailer has the person walking around like a sphere.
Codey: And my brain was, is- is it a sphere? Like, does it look like a sphere?
Codey: Because that would bring me back to the traumatic-ness of, what is it, wild world?
Codey: like the animal crossing.
Codey: I am literally, we, because we just packed everything and moved, we literally packed
Al: Um
Al: Fair enough, you know what you do like though right now on switch
Codey: both of our switches and we're like, man, we never touch these things.
Codey: And then the second I saw this, I went and grabbed my switch and started charging it.
Al: [laughter]
Codey: Especially because of the big bad pharma issue happening right now.
Codey: as well.
Codey: Crank this up, so I'm excited about that.
Al: and we have an update on Haunted Chocolatier.
Al: It's still coming.
Codey: He still do be working on it.
Al: That's, I can't, I, I, it's hilarious.
Al: I actually, I do like these blog posts
Al: that he does every so often,
Al: 'cause like, yeah, I'm still working, don't worry.
Al: I've not forgotten, I've not stopped, I'm still going.
Codey: Yeah
Al: It's, I kind of like that,
Al: 'cause I almost prefer that to the silence
Al: of like Team Cherry or whatever,
Codey: Yeah
Al: where you're just like, is it actually coming?
Codey: You like
Al: Like, probably is, but like we have.
Al: I haven't had confirmation of that in years, like, yeah.
Codey: Maybe one day question mark Wow. No, no
Al: It's been six years since he announced this game now.
Al: Do you think he regrets it?
Al: Announcing it?
Al: No?
Al: Sorry, not six years.
Al: Five years.
Codey: No, I think I mean I think in the he in the thing
Codey: in the blog post, he says something like
Codey: I don't know. Maybe the vibe I got was
Al: Yeah, he definitely talks about how people are supportive, which is good. But you've
Al: got to imagine that when he announced it five years ago, there's no way he was thinking
Codey: >> Yeah, that's true. I definitely, anything, if I was working on a project for, if I was
Codey: about to start a project that was going to take me five years, I would not be talking
Codey: about it. I might be like, I got something in the works. If people were like, what do
Al: No. I don't think I've worked on anything for five years except this podcast and my family.
Codey: you do? Yeah.
Al: Like, there's nothing else I've worked on that long.
Al: I don't think I've even been at a company for five years. Although, will be soon, sadly.
Codey: [laughs]
Al: I mean, if my employer's listening, happily, very happy, happy, happy, happy,
Al: Keep giving me money, give me more money.
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: He deserves more money.
Al: Let's talk about some new games. So first up, we have a game called Keep Watering.
Al: Keep Watering is an incremental game with a cozy, hypnotic loop where every drop of water grows into something
Al: extraordinary.
Codey: Al, what is-- what are your thoughts about that blurb?
Codey: How do you feel about that?
Al: Well, obviously I don't like cozy.
Codey: Mm-hmm.
Al: Extra- I'll let them have extraordinary because
Codey: Hypnotic, though?
Al: hypnotic, hmm.
Al: They're definitely probably going for that.
Codey: I guess, like, when I saw "hypnotic," I was like,
Codey: "What? What are you-- what does this mean?"
Codey: Like, when you're describing--
Codey: if I were to describe a game to you and I were to be like,
Codey: "It's really hypnotic."
Codey: like what what what is the
Codey: invoke for you evoke what how do you feel about that because I was like uh I don't know what that
Al: Yeah, so I guess for me that would mean like, almost like the Tetris effect, where it moves
Al: you into a different state of mind where all you're focusing on is the game and you're
Al: not really conscious fully, but you are just doing the game, you are in the flow, in the
Al: game, you are doing what you need to do. Does that make sense?
Codey: Yeah, I don't know if I want that, but yeah...
Al: I think, Codey, this feels like a follow-up to The Farmer Was Replaced.
Codey: It did it really does like it look watching
Al: I think we need to do this, I think me and you need to play this game when it comes out.
Codey: No, that- yeah, I think this is like the farmer was replaced, but without me having to think about things.
Al: Yeah, yeah, it's not coding just to make it clear. It's not coding, but it definitely gives the like the slowly the incremental build-up of
Codey: Um...
Codey: Yeah.
Codey: Yeah, like it's tiny and then you unlock and especially the decision tree was very the farmer was replaced of like, okay
Al: The dis- yes, yeah. I'm-
Codey: now you're gonna unlock this thing and
Codey: And now suddenly you can use this crop
Codey: But it's there's some some caveats about how to use this crop in relation to other crops like at least that's the vibe
Codey: I'm getting from it. So
Al: - Yeah, I agree.
Codey: Oh my gosh, the publisher's name is lazy otter. Um, I
Al: It's also, also got a Mac bill.
Codey: I did see that.
Al: [laughs]
Codey: You know me, any time I see any of these games, the first thing I look at is does it work on Mac?
Codey: Though I will say, my PC is sitting right here next to me and I'm going to be setting it up at my work desk
Codey: and we're going to find out if that's a mistake.
Codey: I don't think it will be because when I sit down here, there's also a microscope in my face
Codey: and I'm like, "Oh, I could be looking at bugs."
Al: [laughs]
Codey: So I don't think that would be too much of a mistake.
Codey: To play PC games, I was going to say non-Mac, non-Steam Deck games.
Codey: The word for that is PC games.
Codey: I could play them now.
Al: Next up farm and feast. Grow fresh ingredients and run your own little restaurant. Enjoy a peaceful
Al: day that stretches from the field to the table. Plan a fresh menu for a delightful day. Keep your
Al: pantry full and make your customers happy. Earn your own money and build your little world step
Al: by step. [laughter] Am...
Codey: Peaceful? Question mark?
Codey: So, because it looks like the farming, or sorry, the feasting part, the restaurant part
Codey: looks a little bit like Diner Dash, which I don't know if I would call that peaceful.
Codey: Satisfying would be a correct word. I really find those games, those types of games satisfying.
Codey: But I would not say, oh, I want a peaceful moment in time, so I'm going to turn this
Codey: game on.
Al: The cooking minigame looks real weird, where you're like slingshotting things onto a tree.
Codey: Yeah, yeah, the physics in general just look really silly like you're when you're watering
Al: I like, I like the-
Codey: and then you let go of your hose your hose just like rubber bands halfway across your farm.
Al: So what I will say is, you say it looks like it could,
Al: it's not peaceful, it looks more stressful than that.
Al: What I will say is, I don't see a timer
Al: and I don't see them rushing.
Al: So maybe it is just like as you get to it
Codey: Yeah, I want to say like, so the stress part is probably coming from my end then, because
Codey: if I were to play a game like this, even if there's, even if the people that are standing
Codey: in line and waiting are not like getting grumpier and grumpier, even if they're just like chilling,
Codey: I'm still going to be like those people have been waiting a really long time to get a table.
Codey: I need to clean and this other person has been waiting for their food and you know,
Codey: even if it's it would be you know self-imposed I guess and maybe that's something
Codey: I need to work on but I do think this is a game that I want to play.
Al: [laughing]
Al: You're rocking up to your therapist.
Al: So I've been playing a game
Al: and I think I need to work on myself.
Al: [laughing]
Codey: Well, so that's, I mean, that's something like just being in the post-dissertation time frame
Codey: as well. And now that we're done moving, my day, the jobs that I have now, I have multiple,
Codey: but they're all like self, like I get to schedule my own time. There's no deadline. There's not like
Codey: the dissertation deadline lumen. And if I don't get it, then I'm going to get screwed or anything.
Codey: It's just all based on like, how much do I want to slash can I work in a week? And I have, it's
Codey: three different universities. So, um, yeah. And, and so it's, I'm kind of like learning how to
Codey: slow things down and like not have to deal with these like fast paced things. So maybe by the
Codey: time this game comes out, I'll, I'll have that covered. I won't be like, Oh, there's a project
Codey: over there and I need to do it right now, right now, right now. I'm like, no, I'll get to it.
Codey: It's going to be okay. But yeah, chalk me up for this game. I'd play it.
Al: nice nice yeah I think i'm gonna I think i'm think i'm gonna attempt to play
Codey: [laughs]
Al: I like the graphics I really think it looks the graphics definitely give peaceful
Al: they're like almost kind of watercolor-y type graphics also mac os and linux
Codey: Also, Mac OS.
Al: next up is this one of the ones you have an issue with hammer and harvest dwarven roots
Codey: What?
Codey: Have an issue with?
Al: wasn't it's not not this one well you'd said that there were ones that don't count as uh
Codey: Oh.
Codey: Nope.
Codey: This is fine.
Al: for the podcast this is definitely not it because a dwarf farm sim the days of dragon's fire have
Al: ended and now the dwarf king has commissioned you to reclaim the ancient halls grow crops
Al: harvest crystals mine ores and craft works of awe and wonder enrich your home beneath the mountains
Al: before the dwarf king returns to judge your progress oh bye um
Codey: yep nope uh so from so there's a bit of uh like when I imagine dwarves I imagine that like they're
Al: I don't like the graphics on this one
Codey: getting their food through trade not them doing it on their own so because they live underground
Codey: like my dude how are you gonna do that um but yeah I mean that's I also just i'm I have been
Codey: Even averse to not 8-bit, what is it?
Codey: This type of graphic.
Codey: Cel-shaded? Is that what it's called? I don't know.
Al: This is where we need a maker.
Codey: I've just been like a little sick of this type of graphics
Codey: myself, but I do think like it seems rich.
Codey: The world seems pretty rich.
Codey: Like there were a good amount of NPCs.
Codey: The color palette was really interesting for a lot of the stuff.
Codey: The world itself but also like you can make your beard purple or whatever.
Codey: It's something that hasn't been done.
Codey: Starting to be dwarves.
Codey: At least not to my knowledge.
Codey: I would foresee a dwarf game being more mind-based.
Al: - Yeah, you do mine as well.
Al: But yeah, no, I understand where you're coming from.
Al: There does seem to be a market that you go up
Al: to do as well.
Al: And I think, based on what I'm seeing here,
Al: it looks like the farming is above ground.
Al: So you go above ground to farm, and then you go back down.
Codey: Oh, okay, okay.
Al: Just based on that lighting,
Al: 'cause all of the other bits are darker.
Al: And then the farming and the market
Al: are much look light wise.
Al: Like they are above.
Codey: Yeah, I mean, I'm interested to see more of it and hear more of it, but probs not for me
Al: Yeah, yeah, we shall keep an eye on it.
Al: Next up, Isle of Food.
Al: Can you cook when nothing is given to you?
Al: Hunt, fish, gather, and farm your way
Al: to running a stylish island restaurant
Al: in this open world, cozy VR cooking game.
Codey: What does this mean? Can you cook when nothing is given to you?
Al: Oh, but you weren't expecting that.
Al: So I'm guessing the point is like you don't have,
Al: you have to like farm everything,
Al: I'm guessing is the point.
Codey: That's kind of an awkward statement.
Codey: Um, like, yeah, 'cause I just go to the store and buy stuff to [laughs]
Al: Yeah.
Al: Yeah, it's funny because it's like,
Al: also that's kind of like how all farming games work,
Al: nothing's given to you except maybe a plot of land.
Codey: A farm. [laughs]
Al: But like, it looks like an island is given to you here,
Codey: The farm itself.
Al: right, like it's not like that's unique in this aspect.
Codey: Yeah.
Codey: I think the VR aspect is really interesting,
Codey: and it seems like it was really rich in love.
Codey: like the restaurant running side of it and like cooking.
Codey: I had a double take in the,
Codey: when you're walking through and you have a slingshot,
Codey: I was like, what the heck are you using a slingshot for?
Codey: And then you slingshot a chicken
Codey: and the chicken like gets dizzy and falls over
Codey: and then turns into a chicken breast.
Al: [Chuckling]
Codey: It's like, oh my God.
Codey: Especially because I don't think chickens would,
Al: How do you think you get chicken nuggets? Come on!
Codey: no, no, no, I don't think chickens,
Codey: I guess they could be your chickens,
Codey: but I was just like,
Codey: I don't think chickens are just something
Codey: that's gonna just show up on a wild,
Codey: like wild on an island for you to just like go hunt.
Al: I mean, some chickens are wild.
Codey: But not on islands usually.
Al: I don't know, it depends what was on the island before.
Codey: Usually, that's true.
Codey: But I was just, I think I was very shocked.
Codey: I was like, oh, look, you're gonna hunt something.
Codey: And it's a chicken.
Al: Yeah, I don't know whether this is so,
Al: you also shoot a deer with a bow and arrow, but.
Al: This feels quite big for VR.
Al: Like, I don't know, is this gonna feel,
Al: I mean, I know some people really want
Al: like big immersive experiences in VR,
Al: but that's not really what I'm looking for, personally.
Al: But, do you wanna know a secret?
Codey: Yeah. Ooooooh! And? Okay. Well, I'm interested to hear because, so I don't think I'll ever do VR.
Al: I have this game.
Al: I haven't tried it yet.
Al: [laughs]
Al: Yeah.
Codey: I got vertigo a long time ago and it's the same feeling as when you're doing VR and like,
Codey: or when you come out of VR and you have that bit of a "woo" like going back into the real world.
Al: Yeah.
Codey: And that, like, I have like a visceral reaction to that. So, I mean.
Codey: It could just be something that I just need to do more often and get over, but I have decided that no, so far.
Al: Yeah, it's definitely it's definitely a hump you have to get over like when I first started because I got into VR with
Al: Beat Saber because I was like I need to be because I love I love rhythm games and I really miss Guitar Hero
Codey: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. See that?
Codey: Yeah.
Al: which
Al: Yes, they have announced new was it stage tour?
Al: I think is the new game that is a Guitar Hero style game, which I'm currently debating whether I'm going to buy or not
Al: But I was like, "Oh, Beat Saber, this is absolutely for me," and so I got a headset.
Al: And interestingly, I didn't feel sick at all. I did feel sometimes a little bit weird,
Codey: Yeah, that's good.
Al: especially the last, so not the current headset I had, the one before that. It would sometimes
Al: like freeze, but because you're looking through cameras, it's like the world has frozen,
Al: and when you move and the world doesn't move, that really messes up my brain.
Codey: Yeah.
Al: So that was bad, but the newer one is much better for that.
Al: but, uh, what I did have to get
Al: used to is it's really sore on your neck to start with because you've got this massive heavy thing
Codey: Mmm. Yeah.
Al: at the front of your head and there are a couple of ways you can solve that but one of the ways is
Al: you just need to get used to it and like you use it for a short amount of time every day for like
Al: a couple of weeks and the muscles in your neck get stronger and then it's just then it's fine
Al: it's not a problem after that but it's just like that's not what that is not what I thought the
Codey: Yeah, well...
Al: issue would be with VR but it turned out that was the issue for the first couple months was
Al: I had a sore neck most of the time but...
Al: it's just one of these things where when you're not used to using a muscle in that way
Al: it just builds up over time and then you're fine again.
Codey: Yeah, there's a right down the street from me. There's like a
Codey: like an arcade quote-unquote, but it's all like VR and
Al: Hmm. Yeah.
Al: Yeah.
Codey: like
Codey: Big screens are like driving games that have like you sit in a thing and I think it like simulates
Codey: Like the feeling of driving and there's an actual steering wheel and there's actual like gear shifts and stuff that you have to use
Codey: And we were looking into how much it costs.
Codey: To do those things down there.
Codey: Because there's a couple -- Jeff and I would love to race each other.
Codey: In not a vehicle.
Codey: But they do have -- they have some other racing games that have headsets.
Codey: So, you know, maybe if while we're here I feel a little adventurous, I'll try it.
Codey: And then honestly, if I like it, I'm getting Beat Saber.
Codey: Because I'm in the same boat as you.
Al: [laughs]
Codey: My big thing was DDR.
Al: Yeah.
Codey: I loved DDR.
Al: Mm, yeah.
Codey: I played it so much.
Al: Yeah, yeah.
Al: Look, I can't go through an arcade and not play it.
Codey: Yeah.
Codey: Like, I had -- I had the Butterfly.
Al: Still, to this day.
Codey: Of course, everyone played Butterfly.
Codey: But I had it memorized so that I could play it backwards.
Codey: So that I could, like, really mess with one of my friends.
Codey: Because, yeah, we just were always challenging each other to really stupid things.
Codey: And one day I was -- I, like, told them, oh, I bet you can't do it backwards.
Codey: And they were like, you can't.
Codey: And I just, like, started up and turned around.
Codey: I was like, heck, yeah.
Al: Yeah, it's really fun. So I was I was a big snob when Guitar Hero first came out because
Codey: So...
Al: I am I'm a guitarist. I play guitar. That was what I was like. Oh, I was like, oh, it's
Codey: Oh, I didn't know that.
Codey: That's so cool.
Al: not it's not going to be. It's not. It's just stupid. It just makes people think they can
Al: play guitar, blah, blah, blah, blah. And then I didn't play it till like, oh, which one
Al: was it? Three, I think, Legends of Rock. And then I played it and I was like, oh, no, this
Codey: Wow.
Al: This is this is fun
Al: And and it was the sort of thing that I could I
Al: Obsessed over playing through the fire and the flames
Codey: Yup. (laughs)
Al: And
Al: Yeah, I was the same
Al: I got to the point where it was like I could play like I couldn't 100% on on it on expert
Al: But I could play I could do it
Al: I could play it and not die on
Al: Expert and like that was always my like party trick where people were like I was like, oh you got the guitar here
Al: "Let me get a shot" and then you just go like "da-da-da-da-da-da-da" and people
Codey: [Laughs]
Al: are like "woahhh" and you're like "yes, I am so cool". I'm not cool. So much fun.
Codey: Yeah, it was really cool.
Codey: Well, we'll see if the Isle of Food has rhythm games in it.
Al: Yeah, Isle of Food to Guitar Hero and Dance Dance Revolution. Amazing.
Codey: [Laughs]
Al: Next up we have Mead Guard. Oh is this the one you're thinking of? Doesn't count. No
Codey: Nope. This is still... So you're still running a tavern, so...
Al: not this one either. Alright. Chaotic 1-4 player co-op.
Al: Yeah it's not really cottagecore but it is something.
Codey: No, it's, I mean this, this like running a tavern to me still meets the objective and
Codey: like meets the, the whatever calling of this podcast or whatever you want to call it.
Codey: So that, I didn't have an issue with that one.
Codey: I will say it's really funny that like there's a couple of these where it's like and there's
Codey: a theme and we're just gonna be like it's, it's like Viking themed or fantasy themed
Codey: or whatever and there's just like a whole line of these.
Codey: And like I love the idea of doing something like that with multiplayer.
Codey: So a lot of these games are usually like solo.
Codey: Like at the tavern style game, like not tavern style, but like restaurant style games are
Codey: usually just like you doing it on your own.
Codey: And so I like the idea of bringing in other people to do it as well.
Al: Yeah, I will say
Codey: So my one comment is why are the hands so big?
Al: Because you've got to see where they are I will say ten out of ten name Mead Gard, love it, fantastic
Codey: Yes, yes, concur.
Al: Because I will complain when a game has got bad names
Al: So I gotta go out when it's got a great name. Speaking of which, Hammer and Harvest Dwarven Roots. This is a bad name
Al: Give it a better name
Al: Just call it Hammer and Harvest. Why does it need the subtitle?
Codey: Yeah, just yeah, I was gonna say Hammer and Harvest is not that bad at all, but yeah, like the second part is not necessary.
Al: All right, Dungeons and Dragons Long Rest Tavern.
Al: Tired of going on adventures?
Al: Build and run the finest tavern in the coziest corner
Al: of the Dungeons and Dragons universe.
Al: Let heroes face danger while you turn your tails
Al: into your, while you turn their tails into your fortune.
Al: Every legend needs a long.
Codey: I like that this idea, this concept, because I do, um, there's something really intriguing about, like, the running of a tavern, like, running something like that, and, like, there's so many people coming in and out, and they're so crazy, like, they're on such crazy adventures, and you're just like, "Wow, that's cool. I'm just gonna keep running my tavern."
Codey: So, I do like that, and it seems like it has some type of, like, not exploration, 'cause I don't think you're exp-
Codey: But maybe you, like, buy out taverns in other places or something, 'cause there was a map at one point, um...
Al: The map seems to be like there it's almost like you're watching a Dungeons and Dragons game happening in the distance or something
Al: So it says why risk your neck when adventurers are already already looking for glory send heroes across Faerûn
Al: To recover rare ingredients magical curiosities and treasures from their quests just like any great adventure
Al: Their journey is shaped by a roll of the dice with luck skill and fate deciding what they bring
Al: So it's like you send off people to...
Al: ...do an adventure and get you stuff, but you're not doing it yourself and so you see this map and there's...
Al: ...dice rolling around and...
Al: ...yeah, this is the thing that makes me think, "Mmm, I feel like this might be trying to do too much."
Codey: There's a lot in it, for sure, though I will say, in D&D games, but also in Skyrim or whatever,
Codey: you go to the taverns or the inns or whatever to be like, "Hey, have you heard of any quests?
Codey: Have you heard of anyone needing a dragon killed or something?"
Codey: That is the hub of where people post their quests and talk about what they want.
Codey: So I can get that and maybe someone's like, "Oh, I need an ogre killed over..."
Codey: and you're like, "Oh man, they have the best sugar over there and I really want that."
Codey: And so someone will come in and be like, "Oh, is there anything, any killing needing done?"
Codey: and you're like, "Yeah, you should go over here and also bring me back this sugar."
Al: Yeah, I think, if it was something like that, sure, but I feel like this is going to be
Al: more involved than I want. It's going to, I think it's going to feel a bit like, what
Codey: Yeah, that's valid.
Al: was it called? Oh, what was the one me and Chelsea did? No, me and, was it Chelsea? I
Al: lose track. I have too many questions.
Codey: we just keep cropping up like flies what was the game okay
Al: I can't remember the name of the game, Bistro.
Al: It was me and Chelsea, yeah, Bistro.
Al: I feel like it's gonna be like that
Al: where it's just like frustrating
Al: because you have to like go out on these adventures
Al: and do a bunch of stuff and it's like,
Al: I don't really care about this bit.
Al: I wanna go and run.
Al: Like this is, I think, one of my problems
Al: is a lot of these games try and do too much,
Al: too many different things.
Al: And I think it all comes down to the fact
Al: that Stardew did a lot of things, but it did them all well.
Al: And the problem is that every game went,
Al: oh, we're gonna do that many things.
Al: And it's like, yeah, but you're not doing them all well.
Codey: [laughs]
Al: And it's like, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Codey: Pick a, take, stay in your lane.
Codey: [laughs]
Al: And just choose a thing and do it well
Al: rather than doing 10 things badly.
Al: Like, are we running a tavern
Al: or are we doing adventures here?
Al: Like, which are we doing?
Codey: I wonder if it's not something that's required, though, if it's just kind of a side gig.
Al: Yeah.
Codey: So it's not really necessary for you to do.
Al: It did say rare ingredients.
Al: Maybe you're right, yeah.
Codey: Yeah, maybe someone comes in and tries something that you make, and they're like, "Oh man,
Al: I'll give it that.
Al: If that's what it is, then sure, I'll give it it.
Codey: this would go so good with this stuff from the two towns over."
Codey: And then the next time you're sending someone that direction, it's like, "Hey, could you
Codey: also like when you come back da-da-da-da.
Al: We'll have to have a look. We will keep an eye on it. This one's coming out in 2027.
Al: Next up. Anemula... Anemula Nook? Anemula. Anemula.
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: Who knows?
Codey: I- I say- I- I see...
Codey: I see anim- animula...
Codey: animula...
Al: Anemula. Shrink down and reimagine your desk as a whimsical world in Anemula Nook.
Codey: Missed game
Al: Anemula. Anemula Nook. Oh my word! Anemula Nook. Anemula Nook. A cozy miniature life sim.
Codey: Yay.
Al: Craft your homes from odds and ends, grow giant crops, style your outfit of the day,
Al: and explore the enchanting Wuppa Woods. Just remember, minis are always by your side.
Al: See if I have to choose my outfit every single day. I'm gonna hate this game.
Codey: Yeah. So, I think this is the one that I was like, "Does this count?" kind of.
Al: Just, just saying that.
Codey: Like, but, like, I did not get enough of an answer, or, like, my questions were not answered enough in the trailers.
Al: It's a life sim!
Al: Growing crops, how does this not count as a farming game?
Codey: It just doesn't look right. Also, uh, if you watch the, like, first, uh, trailer that's posted,
Codey: because there's, like, the first video that autoplays is, like, a developer playing, like, acting.
Al: For eight minutes long.
Codey: He's, like, actively playing the game, like, starting the game. Yeah, for eight minutes.
Codey: But if you go to the second one, pretty early into that, like, you meet this, like, bunny character
Codey: that's, like, helping get you set up, or whatever. And I am just waiting. I'm gonna, right here and
Codey: now, I'm gonna take bets on how long before that game, or some part of that, gets the ban hammer
Codey: from Animal Crossing. Because it is pretty explicit, uh, like, copying in my mind. Um.
Al: So I think I think I think most of what is similar is not something you can realistically copyright
Al: What I will say though is I think the name
Al: The name feels a little bit stretching it, right like nuke in the name and anim
Al: And it's basically animal crossing cross Tom Nook, right? Like
Codey: They're basically going to say, "Oh, but it's not the word 'animal'."
Al: Yeah, yeah
Al: It feels a little bit the name, but yeah, I mean most of the game is just
Al: you can't really stop that sort of stuff. That's just how games go, but yeah,
Al: the name feels a little bit like you're stretching your luck a little bit there.
Codey: But yeah.
Codey: Yeah, I don't know.
Codey: I watched like two minutes of the first video that autoplays before I realized that it was
Codey: eight minutes long.
Al: [laughs]
Codey: And then I switched to the other one for like 40 seconds.
Codey: And in that almost three minutes of my time it didn't, it didn't, no, it didn't speak
Al: It's not even showing gameplay.
Codey: to me.
Codey: Like I don't know what's going on here.
Codey: I didn't see the things that it says in the blurb that you just said in that.
Codey: I'm not. They lost me.
Al: I think I think I think you gotta you gotta scroll down and see the little
Codey: But yeah, I'm not going to do that.
Al: Clips in the description that shows you the farming and it shows you the other stuff
Al: So like it definitely has farming and it's a life sim. It definitely counts
Codey: I will rescind my criticism of it not counting, but I will retain all other criticism.
Al: Grow giant crops. I mean, yeah criticize the game all you want. Just don't criticize me
Codey: I don't know, no, you're fine.
Codey: I don't know if it's growing giant crops
Al: You
Codey: if you are miniature.
Al: Well giant giant is just no but giant is just a relative term, right?
Codey: You're growing regular size crops.
Al: It's like we have uh, I don't know whether you have them or not
Al: We have a chocolate cause Cadbury's buttons, right?
Codey: Yeah.
Al: And they're little they're little chocolate buttons and then we have Cadbury's giant buttons now. I would say they're not giant
Al: I think they're just slightly bigger than normal
Al: But you can only really call them giant if you're relating them to the normal ones
Al: Right? Like, there are...
Al: They're still, like, the size of, like, what? A 10p coin, right?
Al: Like, they're not... they're not huge.
Al: But they're giant compared to normal buttons.
Codey: Well, in Cad- yeah.
Al: Right? So these are giant compared to the people that are there.
Codey: Yeah.
Al: They're the size of the people, if not bigger!
Al: Look at the size of the blueberry!
Al: It's the size of her head!
Codey: But also the- the name Cadbury, not really giant, but definitely bigger than the other one, is not- it just doesn't roll off the tongue.
Al: Sure. Exactly. So what would you say, craft normal sized crops but actually you're small
Al: so they seem really big? C'mon.
Codey: Yeah, I would actually.
Codey: No, this is- I need to- I'll lock it back. I just-
Al: There's so many things to criticise!
Codey: This game...
Codey: This game rubbed me the wrong way and I needed to overcome that before looking at it again.
Al: It's fine, you probably have plenty of time, because they haven't even given any indication as to when the release date is.
Codey: Yeah, well they gotta they gotta go through litigation with the Animal Crossing first.
Al: [laughs]
Al: Next up, we have Spirit Rancher.
Al: Bet you can't guess what this game is about.
Al: "In this creature-collecting farming sim, your crops are alive!"
Codey: [owl hoots]
Al: "Catch spirits, battle alongside them, use your powers to gather resources and interact with the world"
Al: and build a farm that would keep them happy and productive.
Al: A place they'll call home.
Codey: I think the whole point of farming is that you don't have to do you don't have to harm
Codey: another like animal and then suddenly all of your like it's a it's a creature collecting
Al: [laughter]
Codey: hunting I don't know like what's the equivalent harvesting
Al: It's like a yeah it's like a a non-vegan like one of those like carnivore type people was like oh
Al: what if I had to be vegan oh i'd just eat these crops that are actually animals
Codey: Yeah, yeah, but you but you but you don't eat that like you just collect them that's
Al: it's like a technicality it's like
Al: it's it's a plant i'm eating a plant it's talking to you
Codey: true no no you got a point we do that in real life I get I guess so I don't we can't judge
Codey: too much but if you're like me that's a choice my guy
Al: Oh, we can. I judge all people that do things like me.
Codey: Yeah, I don't know. It sure is a game.
Al: I… nothing about this is calling out to me.
Al: Like nothing looks terrible, but everything just seems a little bit meh.
Al: The graphics, the animations, the description, the name.
Codey: yeah yeah
Al: Why are they spi- why spirit?
Al: Why are they- why are they spirits?
Al: You're growing them.
Al: Oh my goodness, I didn't even notice that, of course, it's just slight magic.
Codey: well because there's another slime was already taken
Al: I just, I don't know why, like, it's, it's...
Al: They're not, they're clearly not spirits, you're growing them.
Al: You can't grow spirits like plants, like, what are you talking about?
Codey: I mean, that's, that's what the people, that's what the spirit farmers, we are technically
Codey: just growing for the spirit farmers to farm us.
Al: Alright, next up, Halcyon Days at Taoyuan. Welcome to Taoyuan Village to heal your loneliness.
Codey: Taowen. Taowen. Yep, pretty much.
Al: Here you can lead a carefree, self-sufficient life. Farm, tame animals, raise livestock,
Al: fish and build a prosperous homestead. Or immerse in village life.
Al: Meet kindred spirits, find love and influence their destinies with your choices.
Codey: [awkward silence]
Codey: *awkward silence* *laughs*
Codey: I mean, technically you do, we do each influence each other's destinies with our choices but
Codey: that is such a weird way to say that and it makes me uncomfy.
Codey: So it says that you can lead a carefree life.
Codey: There are nine major occupations and I loved this actually, I was very happy about this.
Codey: Farming, forestry, animal husbandry, fishing, tailoring, cooking, construction...
Codey: mining or martial arts.
Al: Why why can I marry the animals?
Codey: So I'm really interested in...
Codey: What?
Al: He said animal husbandry
Codey: Oh.
Al: Hey
Codey: Animal wifery.
Al: Husband
Codey: I'm trying to think of...
Codey: Animal spousery.
Codey: Um.
Al: My gender neutral version
Codey: Yeah.
Codey: Uh.
Codey: I like this.
Codey: The depth of all of the different...
Codey: of all of the different
Codey: options. Like the fact that forestry on its own is an option. I like that as someone who works
Codey: in forests. But yeah, we'll see. Well, so I thought of them. So because this is occupations,
Al: Yeah, I wonder how much do you have to do all
Codey: my brain thought of it as like, these are things like you pick one is how I felt.
Al: Yeah, however it does say which one do you want to excel in, not which one do you want
Al: to do, right? So the implication to that for me, what I assumed, is that you're doing a
Al: little bit of everything, but there's one that you like really get good at. In real
Codey: Well, if you had to pick one of these to be really good at, which one would you choose?
Codey: Construction? Construction.
Al: life or in the game? Oh, martial arts, obviously.
Codey: I don't know. We'll see. We have to see more of the game, but also real life. I'm curious.
Codey: I would pick Forestry.
Al: This is assuming I don't need to put in any effort, right? Oh, well, then it doesn't matter, I can just do that. That's just real life. You're just describing real life. What if you could be really good at something by putting in the time and effort into getting good at it? None of them, then. Programming, that's what I did. I don't care if I have to put in the effort. There's no point in this thought experiment. You're just describing life.
Codey: [laughing]
Codey: Yeah.
Codey: There's no programming in here. You have to pick something else.
Codey: [laughing]
Codey: What if these were your options?
Al: What if- what if life-
Al: But there was fewer stuff you could do?
Codey: Yeah, well, what if life only had nine options?
Al: I would kill myself.
Codey: No!
Al: [groans]
Codey: You get to befriend wild creatures.
Codey: [laughing]
Codey: You can either train them as assistants or keep them as companions.
Codey: Por que no los dos?
Codey: Why can't they be your companion that also, like a service...
Al: Don't mix work and pleasure, Codey!
Codey: No!
Codey: Okay, that's it. That's my tweet.
Al: And finally, the game that Codey pointed out that I had missed.
Al: Gaucho Origins. So, this is a spin-off of Gaucho on the Grassland.
Codey: Well, it says origins so it's probably a prequel
Al: A mobile version? A mobile game? A prequel, yes. Experience a cozy adventure inspired by
Al: Brazilian gaucho culture filled with
Al: exploration fantasy and tradition across the Pampas... Pampas... is... was... was...
Codey: Pampas.
Codey: I think, I think that's like a mountain.
Al: Was is das?
Codey: I look it up before I say something stupid.
Al: Fertile low... oh, the grasslands! Grasslands!
Codey: The extensive plains of South America.
Codey: Yeah, okay.
Codey: I was gonna say like a mountain range,
Codey: which is not accurate, but kind of catches the same vibe.
Codey: So I'm gonna give it to myself.
Codey: I did it.
Codey: Congratulations, me.
Al: In a world where ancient legends still echo across the land, a hero prepares for the birth
Codey: Yeah, I need to learn more about it.
Codey: South America.
Al: of his child. When dark forces threaten the peace of the region, he must embrace his role
Al: as a guardian and protect his family and everything he loves. Explore landscapes inspired by southern
Al: Brazil, face fantastic creatures, uncover hidden secrets and follow a story about you.
Codey: Wow, this sounds really cute. I wish I could play it, but it's only on Android
Codey: Yeah, it is
Codey: That's like why
Al: Anyway, uh, that's one for Kevin
Codey: Yeah
Al: Yeah, I'm googling I can't see anything
Codey: for Android. Yeah, I don't see anything.
Codey: Wah-wah. Okay, that's fine. Kevin, tell us about it.
Codey: I don't know if he's Android or Matt or Apple.
Al: I think he's I think I think he think he's Android
Codey: Maybe this is something I need to boot up one of my old Samsung phones for.
Codey: Though I feel like, can you, you probably need like an active
Codey: cell account for that. Like I couldn't, I could just boot it up and join the
Codey: the Wi-Fi and then I'm not gonna do that.
Al: - Yeah, yeah.
Codey: Let's be honest.
Al: [laughing]
Codey: [laughs]
Al: - Ah, but what if you did?
Codey: Nope.
Al: - All right, that's an episode.
Codey: We did an episode, you guys.
Al: - A nice short episode.
Codey: Is it? Was it actually?
Al: - No, of course it wasn't.
Codey: I'm sorry.
Codey: I'm sorry, it's me.
Al: - It's not your fault, it's not your fault.
Codey: I'm- I'm the problem.
Al: - Thank you, Codey, for joining me.
Al: Is there anything you would like to share with the audience?
Codey: You should learn about your local cockroach species so that if you have one in your home
Codey: and your landlord tries to tell you that you don't know what you're talking about.
Codey: She didn't say that.
Codey: A lot of this is me projecting.
Codey: Then you can be confident in your own ability to identify cockroaches and know that you
Codey: are right, even though it doesn't really matter.
Al: Cockroaches are apparently very uncommon.
Codey: Oh, interesting.
Codey: Well, luck-
Codey: So the- I will- the end of the story, I guess, is that no matter what cockroach species,
Codey: like she said it's a P.A. woodroach, but it's actually a tawny roach, doesn't matter. They
Codey: aren't invasive, or they aren't pests. They don't- they'll- they might show up in homes,
Codey: like, incidentally, but they're not, like, a pest. So it doesn't really matter.
Al: This is what I find so funny is like she's still arguing with you despite the fact that
Al: it now doesn't matter.
Codey: Yeah. And so I just, like, hit a point where I was like, "Okay." I was like, you know,
Codey: you know, just a heads up that I saw this and, and, but, but...
Codey: you know, it doesn't seem like it matters.
Codey: And she's like, well, I'm going to talk to my exterminator.
Codey: And not, and then she, yeah, basically just echoed what I said,
Codey: except for said the wrong species and insinuated that I brought it.
Al: You can find the podcast on Tumblr and on Blue Sky at THSPod.
Al: You can also see our clips, our daily clips there and on YouTube at THSPod.
Codey: Are daily clips?
Al: I've been clipping from the podcast episodes, posting them up one a day. You know it.
Codey: Have you?
Codey: Wow.
Al: Some of them have been doing better than others.
Codey: Do what?
Codey: Wondering if I want to-
Codey: Okay, cool.
Al: You can also send us feedback from our website, harvestseason.club.
Al: One of the many, many, many millions of games that were announced at Gamescom that you are excited for.
Al: Also on the website you can find links to everything to do with the podcast, including a link to our Patreon, patreon.com/thspod,
Al: where you can support the podcast, keep us buying games.
Al: You get access to the Slack, where we talk about stuff and make fun of different people, depending on the week.
Codey: On the Slack this week, I will post a photo of my most -- of today's morning walk.
Codey: With New York City in the background.
Al: And the cockroach.
Codey: Okay.
Codey: I will also post the cockroach.
Al: I wanna see the cockroach.
Codey: I didn't post it -- I didn't post it in the other thing -- like, in anywhere online except
Codey: for with my entomology folks because I didn't want people to get jump scared.
Codey: But I guess I can spoiler it or thread it or whatever.
Codey: Yep.
Al: You also get access to our bonus episodes of the podcast some soon
Codey: I'll do that.
Codey: We really do. Well, what if I told you I am now actually, like, in the location I will be in for a hot minute, so I will actually have time.
Al: Kevin and Codey keep promising episodes and then not recording it
Al: >> Nice. Good. Do it. Thank you, Codey. I love you. All right. I think that's everything
Codey: Okay.
Codey: I love you too, friend.
Al: to do with the podcast. Thank you, Codey, again, for joining me. Thank you, listeners,
Codey: Thank you, Al, for having me.
Al: for listening. And until next time, have a good harvest.
Codey: Have a good harvest.
Theme Tune: The Harvest Season is created by Al McKinley with support from our Patrons including our
Codey: Al, Al, Al.
Theme Tune: Pro Farmers Kevin, Stuart and Elisa. Our art is done by Micah the Brave and our music is
Theme Tune: done by Nick Burgess. Feel free to visit our website HarvestSeason.club for show notes
Theme Tune: and links to things we discussed in this episode.
Codey: yep and tell it I don't know I was gonna come up with something stupid continue
Al: Also on our website, oh, you just started talking before.
Codey: correct I was like i'm gonna fill space with words
Al: Never a problem when we're already out an hour and a half.